Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 8 and District 8 Locals, 1936-1957 UE.4.1.8
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 8 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1116
    - Local 1116 Robert Kirkwood Incoming Correspondence, December 29, 1937 - October 9, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Carey Secretary Regarding Missed Meeting, January 25, 1938; 2.
      - Carey Regarding Mass Meeting, February 5, 1938; 3.
      - Carey Regarding Labor Unity, March 21, 1939; 4.
      - Chase Regarding Trials, Undated; 5.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Mailing List, January 12, 1937; 6.
      - Emspak Regarding Supplies, June 28, 1937; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, July 14, 1937; 8.
      - Emspak Regarding UE Convention, August 30, 1937; 9.
      - Emspak Regarding Per Capita and CIO, December 1, 1937; 10.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, December 23, 1937; 11.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 1223 Wages, January 21, 1938; 12.
      - Emspak Regarding Constitution, February 2, 1938; 13.
      - Emspak Regarding Transfers and Building Trades, February 23, 1938; 14.
      - Emspak Regarding Strikes, June 2, 1938; 15.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, Per Capita and Strike, June 22, 1938; 16.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, Per Capita and Strike, June 27, 1938; 17.
      - Emspak Regarding Strikes and Per Capita, July 22, 1938; 18.
      - Emspak Regarding UE Constitution, October 6, 1938; 19.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, October 12, 1938; 20.
      - Emspak Regarding Maytag Defense Fund, October 31, 1938; 21.
      - Emspak Regarding Strike Finances, December 6, 1938; 22.
      - Emspak Regarding Dues and National Labor Relations Board, March 2, 1939; 23.
      - Emspak Regarding Bonding, August 22, 1939; 24.
      - Emspak Regarding Strikes and Bonding, October 9, 1939; 25.
    - Local 1116 Robert Kirkwood Incoming Correspondence, November 17, 1938 - August 7, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - S. Kelly Regarding Publicity, November 17, 1938; 1.
      - Kelly Regarding Publicity and Education, November 23, 1938; 2.
      - James Matles Regarding Strikes and Negotiations, August 25, 1938; 3.
      - Matles Regarding Maytag Profits, November 10, 1938; 4.
      - Matles Regarding Wages, Organization and Easy Washing Machine, December 15, 1938; 5.
      - Matles Regarding Negotiations, December 29, 1938; 6.
      - Matles Regarding Negotiations, January 9, 1939; 7.
      - Matles Regarding Trials and Negotiations, May 17, 1939; 8.
      - Matles Regarding Visit, July 31, 1939; 9.
      - Matles Regarding New York Visit, August 24, 1939; 10.
      - William Mitchell Regarding Supplies, April 13, 1938; 11.
      - International Vice President Regarding Strikes, October 6, 1938; 12.
      - International Vice President Regarding Organization, Negotiations and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, April 7, 1939; 13.
      - International Vice President Regarding District Officers, Negotiations and Grievances, August 7, 1939; 14.
    - Local 1116 Robert Kirkwood Outgoing Correspondence, June 1, 1937 - May 25, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Robert Kirkwood to UE Regarding Supplies, June 1, 1937; 1.
      - Kirkwood to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, June 24, 1937; 2.
      - Kirkwood to James Carey Regarding Organization and Supplies, June 25, 1937; 3.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding District and Per Capita, June 30, 1937; 4.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Organization and Finances, July 1, 1937; 5.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 16, 1937; 6.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding UE Convention, August 27, 1937; 7.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding UE Convention, August 31, 1937; 8.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Finances and Farmers, Setpember 22, 1937; 9.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, November 16, 1937; 10.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, November 22, 1937; 11.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, November 29, 1937; 12.
      - Kirkwood to Carey Regarding Carey Visit, December 14, 1937; 13.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 14, 1937; 14.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 14, 1937; 15.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, December 20, 1937; 16.
      - Kirkwood to James Matles Regarding Mass Meeting, January 5, 1938; 17.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Mass Meeting, January 19, 1938; 18.
      - Kirkwood to Carey Regarding Mass Meeting, January 31, 1938; 19.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Transfers, February 8, 1938; 20.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Publicity, February 15, 1938; 21.
      - Kirkwood to Carey, April 1, 1938; 22.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, May 19, 1938; 23-24.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Strikes, May 25, 1938; 25.
    - Local 1116 Robert Kirkwood Outgoing Correspondence, June 20, 1938 - April 6, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Robert Kirkwood to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Strikes, June 20, 1938; 1.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Strikes and Per Capita, June 24, 1938; 2.
      - Kirkwood to UE Regarding Strikes with Memo, July 15, 1938; 3.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Supplies, August 8, 1938; 4.
      - Kirkwood to James Matles Regarding Grievances, Organization, Unemployment, Political Action, Officers and Trials, November 14, 1938; 5.
      - Kirkwood to William Sentner Regarding Unemployment and Seniority, Decebmer 9, 1938; 6.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Wages, December 17, 1938; 7.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Organization, Officers, Per Capita and Unemployment, Febaruy 13, 1939; 8.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Wages, February 16, 1939; 9.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Organization, Febraury 26, 1939; 10.
      - Kirkwood to William Sentner Regarding Negotiations and Grievances with Kirkwood Letter to Matles, March 29, 1939; 11.
      - Kirkwood to Sentner Regarding Unemployment Negotiations and Organization with Kirkwood Letter to Matles, April 4, 1939; 12.
      - Kirkwood to Sentner Regarding Grievances, Negotiations and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Organization, April 6, 1939; 13.
    - Local 1116 Robert Kirkwood Outgoing Correspondence, April 20 - August 22, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Robert Kirkwood to Julius Emspak Regarding UE News with Newspaper Clippings, April 20, 1939; 1.
      - Kirkwood to James Matles Regarding Wages and Unemployment, April 21, 1939; 2.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Negotiations and Organization, April 26, 1939; 3.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Negotiations and Check-off, May 2, 1939; 4.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Trials, May 16, 1939; 5.
      - Kirkwood to George Umbriet Regarding Negotiations, May 20, 1939; 6.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Negotiations, Organization and Boycott with Clippings, May 24, 1939; 7.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Negotiations, May 25, 1939; 8.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Women, May 27, 1939; 9.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Negotiations, July 29, 1939; 10.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Organization and Negotiations with August 8, 1939, Umbriet Letter to Wilbert Allison, August 9, 1939; 11.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 15, 1939; 12-13.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Finances, August 22, 1939; 14.
    - Local 1116 Maurice Young Incoming Correspondence, June 16, 1942 - April 3, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, March 1, 1949; 1.
      - Joe Dermondy Regarding Wages and Wage Control Board, January 3, 1944; 2.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, February 7, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak Regarding Wages, July 22, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak Regarding Bonding, July 10, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, July 10, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, September 12, 1946; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding Locals 702 and 1103, December 5, 1946; 8.
      - Emspak Regarding Farm Equipment Workers, February 15, 1950; 9.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 750 and Strikes, April 3, 1950; 10.
      - James Matles Regarding Organization, June 16, 1942; 11.
      - Matles Regarding Organization and Power and Light, June 29, 1942; 12.
      - Matles Regarding Wages, Women and Overtime, October 14, 1942; 13.
      - Alice Smith Regarding Contracts, Belmont Radio and Local 149, undated; 14.
      - David Scribner Regarding Affiliation with Emspak Letter, January 18, 1944; 15.
    - Local 1116 Maurice Young Outgoing Correspondence, June 5, 1942 - December 12, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Maurice Young to James Matles Regarding Membership Drive and Staff Members, June 5, 1942; 1.
      - Young to Matles Regarding Organization and New York Power and Light, June 15, 1942; 2.
      - Young to Matles Regarding Negotiations and Wages, October 5, 1942; 3.
      - Young to Matles Regarding Negotiations, Women, Wages and Overtime, October 8, 1942; 4.
      - Young to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Wage Control Board and Negotiations, January 31, 1943; 5.
      - Young to Julius Emspak Regarding Contracts and Advertising Novelty, March 11, 1943; 6.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Negotations and Wages with Piece Rates on War Work, July 3, 1943; 7.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 13, 1944; 8.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Organization and Negotiations, February 3, 1944; 9.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding WCB and Rate Progressions, December 27, 1944; 10.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 2, 1945; 11.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, July 6, 1945; 12.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Publicity, September 18, 1945; 13.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Publicity, April 18, 1946; 14.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, September 5, 1946; 15.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding PAC, September 18, 1946; 16.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding PAC, October 3, 1946; 17-18.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding PAC, November 13, 1946; 19.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding PAC, November 21, 1946; 20.
      - Young to William Sentner Regarding Organization and Belmont Radio, December 12, 1946; 21.
    - Local 1116 Maurice Young Outgoing Correspondence, January 28, 1947 - September 1, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Maurice Young to Julius Emspak Regarding Publicity, January 28, 1947; 1.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, November 17, 1947; 2.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding PAC, December 18, 1947; 3.
      - Young to Harry Truman Regarding Blacklisting, September 2, 1948; 4.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Strikes and Packinghouse Workers, February 1, 1949; 5.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, March 7, 1949; 6.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Radio Broadcasts, April 4, 1949; 7.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Vacation, July 6, 1949; 8.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Mergers, FE-UE and Negotiations, February 11, 1950; 9.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Local 750, March 28, 1950; 10.
      - Young to Emspak Regarding Officers, September 1, 1950; 11.
    - Local 1116 Incoming Correspondence, May 25, 1937 - January 24, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - James Carey to Alex Barbour Regarding Carey Visit, September 10, 1940; 1.
      - Carey to C.E. Allan, September 27, 1940; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Ernest White Regarding Organization, May 25, 1937; 3.
      - Emspak to Roy Barnes Regarding Finances, December 31, 1937; 4.
      - Emspak to George Albee Regarding Per Capita and Stirkes, January 12, 1940; 5.
      - Emspak to Albee Regarding National Labor Relations Board, March 18, 1940; 6.
      - Emspak to Albee Regarding Per Capita, April 6, 1940; 7.
      - Emspak to Albee, July 17, 1940; 8.
      - Emspak to Albee Regarding UE News and Boycott, January 15, 1941; 9.
      - Emspak to Barbour Regarding UE News and Boycott, January 22, 1941; 10.
      - Emspak to Albee Regaridng UE News, March 10, 1941; 11.
      - Emspak to Albee Regarding Finances, May 22, 1941; 12.
      - Emspak to Jacob Miller Regarding Withdrawal Cards, January 24, 1946; 13.
    - Local 1116 Incoming Correspondence, October 8, 1937 - February 26, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - James Matles to Roy Barnes Regarding Transfers, October 8, 1937; 1.
      - Matles to Dorothy Wheeler Regarding Finances, September 15, 1939; 2.
      - Matles to Willis Steinberger, March 5, 1940; 3.
      - Matles to George Albee Regarding Staff Members and Organization, August 17, 1940; 4.
      - Matles to Albee Regarding Staff Members, August 26, 1940; 5.
      - Matles to Albee Regarding Staff Members and Negotiations, October 4, 1940; 6.
      - Matles to Albee Regarding Matles Visit, October 29, 1940; 7.
      - Matles to W.K. Steinberger Regarding Staff Members, January 20, 1941; 8.
      - Matles to Steinberger Regarding Gibson Refrigerator Organization, January 22, 1941; 9.
      - Matles to Albee Regarding Matles Visit, January 24, 1941; 10.
      - Matles to Albee Regarding Negotiations, February 19, 1941; 11.
      - Matles to E.B. Passmore Regarding Staff Members, March 5, 1941; 12.
      - Matles to Alex Barbour Regarding Contracts and Wages, May 14, 1941; 13.
      - David Ratner to Bob Roberts Regarding Finances, February 26, 1941; 14.
    - Local 1116 Outgoing Correspondence, October 4, 1937 - January 20, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - George Albee to James Matles Regarding Finances, September 20, 1939; 1.
      - Albee to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Unemployment, December 30, 1939; 2.
      - Albee to Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board, March 9, 1940; 3.
      - Albee to Emspak Regarding Boycott, April 5, 1940; 4.
      - Albee to James Carey Regarding NLRB and Carey Visit, July 15, 1940; 5.
      - Albee to Carey Regarding Carey Visit, August 17, 1940; 6.
      - Albee to Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 24, 1940; 7.
      - Albee to Matles Regarding Membership Drive and Staff Members, Ocotber 9, 1940; 8.
      - Albee to Matles Regarding Matles Visit, January 24, 1941; 9.
      - Albee to Matles Regarding Matles Visit and Contracts, February 4, 1941; 10.
      - Albee to Matles Regarding NLRB and Negotiations, September 14, 1941; 11.
      - C.E. Allan to Carey Regarding Employment, September 18, 1940; 12.
      - Allan to Carey Regarding Employment with Allan Letter to U.S. Civil Service Commission, October 19, 1940; 13.
      - Alex Barbour to Carey Regarding UE Convention, August 22, 1940; 14.
      - Barbour to Emspak Regarding Washing Machine Industry, January 7, 1941; 15.
      - Roy Barnes to UE Regarding Transfers, October 4, 1937; 16.
      - Seibert Chesnutt to Emspak Regarding Boycott, May 14, 1938; 17.
      - J.G. Gamble to Matles Regarding Negotiations, May 15, 1940; 18.
      - Holly Hal to H.E. Regarding NLRB and Factionalism, May 17, 1940; 19.
      - Jacob Miller to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 20, 1946; 20.
      - P.N. Paulson to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 27, 1937; 21.
      - P.O. to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 4, 1938; 22.
    - Local 1116 Outgoing Correspondence, May 20, 1937 - January 17, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - E.B. Passmore to James Carey Regarding Finances, February 19, 1941; 1.
      - W.R. Steinberger to James Matles Regarding Gibson Organization, January 8, 1940; 2.
      - Steinberger to Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 29, 1941; 3.
      - Archie Thompson to UE Regarding Organization, April 17, 1937; 4.
      - M.B. Turney to UE Regarding Organization and Supplies, January 17, 1946; 5.
      - Dorthy Wheeler to Matles Regarding Address Change, September 13, 1939; 6.
      - Wheeler to Julius Emspak Regarding Sentner Trial, October 4, 1939; 7.
      - Ernest White to Carey Regarding Organization, May 20, 1937; 8.
    - Local 1116 Per Capita Reports, July 1937 - July 1938 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Local 1116 Delinquency and Suspension Notices, November 1937 - July 1938 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Local 1116 Income and Expense Report and Dues, March 31, 1939 - August 14, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Local 1116 Newspapers, July 16, 1938, October 2, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Shop Bulletin, July 16, 1938; 1.
      - Des Moines Federationist, October 2, 1941; 2.
    - Local 1116 Leaflets, July 19, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Proclamation Regarding Strike, July 19, 1938; 1.
      - Authorization Cards, 1938; 2.
      - "Attention Automatic Employees" Regarding Organization, Undated; 3.
    - Local 1116 Newspaper Clippings, August 6, 1938 - December 1942 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - "National CIO Leader Arrives", August 6, 1938; 1.
      - "Maytag Union Widen Talks Basis," Des Moines Register, August 7, 1938; 2.
      - "Hints Pact May Be Near," Des Moines Tribune, August 8, 1938; 3.
      - "Iowa Union Man's Indictment for Syndicalism Dismissed", November 1938; 4.
      - "Labor Troubles and the Church," Advance, June 1, 1939; 5.
      - "Iowa's Criminal Syndicalism," Des Moines Register, October 10, 1939; 6.
      - "One to be Applauded," Des Moines Tribune, May 17, 1940; 7.
      - "Maytag Plant Wage Increase" with Bill W. Letter to Bob, May 13, 1941; 8.
      - "Everybody Buy Bonds" with Maurice Young Letter to Julius Emspak, December 16, 1942; 9.
      - "Advertising Novelty and Employees Cited for War Jobs," Newton Daily News, March 18, 1944; 10.
      - "Griggs New UE Chief", Undated; 11.
    - Local 1116 Press Release Regarding Red-baiting and Photo of Loyal Sisters Drill Team, February 20, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Local 1116 Organization, May 25 - June 2, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Robert B. Logsdon to James Carey, May 25, 1937; 1.
      - Logsdon to Carey, May 28, 1937; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Logsdon, June 2, 1937; 3.
    - Local 1116 Strike, May 27 - July 14, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Julius Emspak to William Sentner, May 27, 1938; 1.
      - Sentner to Emspak, May 31, 1938; 2.
      - Contempt Citation, June 22, 1938; 3.
      - UE Letter to Des Moines Register, June 28, 1938; 4.
      - James Matles to Sentner, June 28, 1938; 5.
      - Sentner to Matles, June 29, 1938; 6.
      - Matles to Maytag Washing Machines, June 29, 1938; 7.
      - Maytag to Matles, June 29, 1938; 8.
      - Matles to Sentner, June 30, 1938; 9.
      - Matles to Sentner, July 2, 1938; 10.
      - Sentner to Emspak, July 6, 1938; 11.
      - James Carey to Emspak, July 7, 1938; 12.
      - Carey to Emspak, July 8, 1938; 13.
      - Emspak to Carey, July 13, 1938; 14.
      - Bunting to Emspak, July 14, 1938; 15.
    - Local 1116 Strike, July 15 - 21, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Jonathan Eddy to N.C. Kraschel, July 15, 1938; 1.
      - Mervyn Rathborne to Kraschel, July 15, 1938; 2.
      - James Matles to James Carey, July 15, 1938; 3.
      - Julius Emspak with Address List, July 15, 1938; 4.
      - Emspak with Address List, July 15, 1938; 5.
      - Lewis Berne to Kraschel, July 16, 1938; 6.
      - Letter to Emspak, July 16, 1938; 7.
      - H.C. Fremming to Kraschel, July 16, 1938; 8.
      - Arbitration Board Recommendations, July 16, 1938; 9.
      - Emspak to Edwin Bunting, July 16, 1938; 10.
      - Bunting to Emspak, July 16, 1938; 11.
      - Court Order, July 16, 1938; 12.
      - Charles Howard to Emspak, July 18, 1938; 13.
      - Matles to William Sentner, July 18, 1938; 14.
      - Philip Murray to Kraschel with Murray to Emspak, July 18, 1938; 15.
      - Francis Henson to Emspak with Homer Martin to Kraschel, July 16, 1938, July 21, 1938; 16.
      - P.H. VanGelder to Kraschel, July 21, 1938; 17.
    - Local 1116 Strike, July 25 - August 16, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - William Sentner to Julius Emspak, July 25, 1938; 1.
      - Sentner to Emspak, July 27, 1938; 2.
      - Sentner to James Carey, August 1, 1938; 3.
      - Sentner to James Matles, August 1, 1938; 4.
      - William Mauseth to Matles, August 4, 1938; 5.
      - Matles to Mauseth, August 4, 1938; 6.
      - Harold Christoffel to Nelson Kraschel, August 4, 1938; 7.
      - C.R.C. to Wilbert Allison, August 4, 1938; 8.
      - Kenneith Cole to Emspak, August 5, 1938; 9.
      - Emspak to Cole, August 5, 1938; 10.
      - Carey to Matles, August 5, 1938; 11.
      - Carey to Sentner, August 5, 1938; 12.
      - Emspak to Sentner, August 5, 1938; 13.
      - Matles to Emspak, August 8, 1938; 14.
      - Lee Pressman to Carey, August 9, 1938; 15.
      - Carey to Matles, August 9, 1938; 16.
      - Executive Vice President to Emspak, August 12, 1938; 17.
      - Ed Beal to Jim, August 13, 1938; 18.
      - Matles to Emspak, August 17, 1938; 19.
    - Local 1116 Strike, August 17 - December 8, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Council Minutes Excerpt, August 17, 1938; 1.
      - Meyer Edelman to Maytag, August 24, 1938; 2.
      - Edelman to William Sentner, September 7, 1938; 3.
      - Sentner to Edelman with Edelman to James Carey, September 7, 1938; 4.
      - James Pascoe to James Matles, September 13, 1938; 5.
      - Emspak to All Locals with September 18, 1938, General Executive Board Report on Maytag Defense Fund, September 28, 1938; 6.
      - Ed Beal to Matles, October 2, 1938; 7.
      - Stay Bond, December 8, 1938; 8.
      - James Carey Draft with Memo, 1938; 9.
      - Wage Assignment, 1938; 10.
      - Maytag Financial Report, 1938; 11.
    - Local 1116 Reorganization and NLRB Case, March 4 - November 23, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - George Umbreit to Julius Emspak, March 4, 1939; 1.
      - Estelle Frankfurter to John Connolly, May 1, 1939; 2.
      - C.I. McNutt to James Carey, May 9, 1939; 3.
      - Carey to McNutt, May 11, 1939; 4.
      - James Shields to Matles, July 5, 1939; 5.
      - Matles to Robert Weiner, August 12, 1939; 6.
      - Matles to Weiner, August 15, 1939; 7.
      - W.R. Steinberger to Matles, September 20, 1939; 8.
      - Steinberger to William Sentner, Septmeber 27, 1939; 9.
      - Umbreit Secretary to Matles, October 6, 1939; 10.
      - General Vice President to Steinberger, November 13, 1939; 11.
      - Sentner to Matles, November 13, 1939; 12.
      - Steinberger to Sentner with Agreement on Rehiring, Case President to Umbreit and Organizational Program for Local 1116, November 23, 1939; 13.
      - Report on Conditions, 1939; 14.
    - Local 1116 Reorganization and NLRB Case, April 28, 1940 - May 14, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Memo with Newspaper Clippings, Deptartment 9 Workers, Union Rehire List, Original Cases, Amended Charge List, Lay-off List, Membership Statistics and Memo, April 28, 1940; 1.
      - James Matles to James Morgan, June 26, 1940; 2.
      - Morgan to Matles, June 27, 1940; 3.
      - Steinberger Report, 1940; 4.
      - Special Stewards Meeting Questions, Undated; 5.
      - Julius Emspak to Victor Levitt, January 15, 1941; 6.
      - Levitt to Emspak, January 16, 1941; 7.
      - William Sentner to Matles with Organizational Program, February 13, 1941; 8.
      - Agnes to James Carey, April 3, 1941; 9.
      - Emspak to Sentner, May 14, 1941; 10.
    - Local 1116 Reorganization and NLRB Case, September 25, 1941 - January 13, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - William Sentner to James Matles, October 1, 1941; 1.
      - Department of Concilliation Report, September 25, 1941; 2.
      - Sentner to John Steelman with Sentner to Albert Fitzgerald, January 13, 1942; 3.
    - Local 1116 Inter-union Rivalry and Officers, February 6 - March 21, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - William Sentner to Julius Emspak, February 6, 1951; 1.
      - Sentner to David Ratner, February 23, 1951; 2.
      - Sentner to James Matles, March 21, 1951; 3.
    - Local 1116 Correspondence, May 26, 1937 - December 13, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - Robert Logsdon to James Carey Regarding Organization and Adding Machines, May 26, 1937; 1.